Hi, I'm Art Malov from Your Dating Coach in New York City.
And, I'm the author of Park Bench Dating.
In this clip, we're going to talk about how to buy someone a drink.
And, there is few different elements.
You see, most guys think they wanna, they should buy a drink right away.
The first opening line for them, is, hey, can I buy you a drink?
And, that's not the right way to do it.
Because, what it tells the girl is, you're just trying to buy her attention.
You're just trying to make buying a drink for her, sort of, bargaining for her attention.
So, don't buy a drink in the first five minutes.
But, until you spend some time with the girl, and, for, let's say fifteen minutes, twenty minutes, then you can actually say, hey listen, can I get you a drink?
And, you, when you're already getting yourself a drink.
You don't be like, oh, can I just get you a drink?
Say, hey listen, I'm going to get a drink, and, you know, you can get, well, what do you want?
And then you can say, you can get us, well what do you want, you can get us next round.
So, what you're emphasizing here, is, it's, you're not trying to buy her time.
What you're doing is, you're putting yourself on equal footing.
Cause "wh", as soon as the girl hears, hey, can I buy you a drink, she thinks, what a wuss.
And, we don't want that.
We want, so you know like, she wants to see a confident, relaxed guy.
And so, don't buy a drink in five minutes, but buying a drink, you know, in fifteen, twenty minutes, is fine.
As long as you do it in correct way.
This is Art Malov and this has been, How To Buy Someone A Drink.